the trump administration has been and continues to be absolutely detrimental to women's health
care and women's health care progress um and nobody's talking about it so let's talk about
what's going on also i'm really sorry for all the background noise i cannot figure out what it is
so the health care system has been inequitable towards women since the beginning this isn't new
to the trump administration these inequities exist within budgeting research misdiagnosis
neglect of women's symptoms um and although this is not new to the trump administration
the trump administration has been rolling back years and years of progress the trump
The Trump administration has made extreme cuts to the CDC, removing a lot of people from their positions,
and an inadequate amount come from reproductive health care units.
Additionally, the administration has made major cuts to Title X family planning legislation,
and these cuts predominantly hurt low-income women.
I also think it's super important to know when we're talking about female health care,
that female health care is not solely contraceptive and abortion access,
it's understanding and researching the female body as a whole.
For example, those Title 10 cuts do impact women's access to contraceptives and access
to abortion, but it also limits women's access to wellness and cancer screenings.
Women's health being underfunded and under-researched is no accident, it's used as a control tactic,
and women are not talking about it enough and are not angry enough about it.
So with that, mobilize in any way you can, register to vote, midterm elections are coming
up in so many states across the country this month, call your senators, get involved locally,
Whatever you can do, do it, because we cannot let the Trump administration keep hurting
women.
That's all she wrote.